DIMITRIS RAMMOS

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

Hello, I am 21 years old and I live in Athens. I am a Junior Software Developer at Netcompany-Intrasoft. I am a Full Stack Developer and we coding with Java. I am an undergraduate student in Department of Informatics and Telecommunications, University of Athens. I am at 4th year of studies.

CONTACT



- 🔽 jrammos@outlook.com.gr
- www.linkedin.com/in/dimitrisrammos/
- <u>DimitrisRammos</u>
- My portfolio

EDUCATIONS

Department of Informatics and Telecommunications, NKUA

COMPUTER SCIENCE, OCT 2019 - PRESENT



SKILLS

- Rust
- C/C++
- Java
- MySQL
- Python
- HTML/CSS/JavaScript
- Git
- Assembly

EXPERIENCE

Check-In Agent

GOLDAIR HANDLING, JUL 2021 - SEP 2021 - HERAKLION, GREECE

I was Check-In Agent for Aegean Airlines

Associate Software Engineer

WAPPIER, AUG 2022 - FEB 2023 - ATHENS, GREECE

I am a Backend developer and I code in Rust.

Junior Software Developer

NETCOMPANY-INTRASOFT, FEB 2023 - PRESENT - ATHENS, GREECE

I am a Full Stack developer and I am working on hospital medical file project(Java, Spring, PrimeFaces).

PROJECTS

- Tic Tac Toe_- Game
- Role Playing Game Terminal Game
- Graph Coloring Project Project
- Artificial-Intelligence Project
- Compilers Project
- My Portfolio My WebPage

LANGUAGES

HOBBIES

- Greek Mother Tongue
- English Lower

Gym Box